onetermmore.com 2015-04-02

# One Term More

"ONE TERM MORE" PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy statement sets out how One Term More.com protects information you knowingly or unknowingly give us when you visit our site. We're committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide information by which you can be identified (and that would ONLY be if/when buying a T-shirt), be assured it will only be used in strict accordance with this policy.

This policy is effective August 1, 2012.  

GENERAL POLICY  
We will neither collect nor store ANY information about those visiting our site. Period. It is NOT our intent to track by name, IP address or any other means those who visit us or to market or solicit those who do. We're not compiling lists of any kind for any present or future use or reference. (Some would say that's a missed opportunity. We would say it's about respecting people's privacy.) 

We'll certainly count the number of visitors we host, but will have NO record of who they are or how often they visit.  

T-SHIRTS  
Anyone purchasing a Tee will necessarily be providing name/address/credit card information, but will be doing so directly and discreetly to PayPal in a secure transaction. 

COOKIES: WE DON'T USE 'EM!   
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive to analyze web traffic, let you know when you visit a particular site and allow web apps to respond to you as an individual, gathering and remembering information about your preferences. WE WON'T BE DOING THAT! 

LINKS TO OTHER SITES  
Our site contains a few links to sites of those associated with this project. You may or may not wish to click on them. There is no commercial gain for us by your doing so and we won't know if you do. 

However, once you've used these links to leave our site, remember we don't have any control over theirs and therefore can't be responsible for the protection & privacy of any information that you may intentionally or inadvertently provide while visiting them. Needless to say, they're not governed by our privacy policy. 

You should always exercise caution and examine the privacy statement applicable to any websites you visit.  

CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
Whenever you are asked to fill out a form (in our case, it's limited to using PayPal to purchase a Tee), look for the box that you can click-on to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anyone for direct marketing purposes. 

WE won't be compiling ANY information about you so can't sell, distribute or lease anything about you to anyone.   

We hope you enjoy our site!
